Hello hello everyone today we are giving comparison
about Tata AIG's Medical Plus Super Top Pay vs
ICICI Lombard's Health Booster Super
Top Pay. We are general insurance companies and many
travel companies. Till a few years ago these
companies did not focus on major health insurance
related products but
both the companies are focusing a lot which is
very good for all of us. So the
subscription of these
products is so big that we hate it. The
problem is inch and inch in Tata Plus is between 3 lakhs to 1
crore and in ICICI Lombard
it is 5 lakhs to 50 lakhs. If we
talk about one year, two years and three years in the company then Tata has 12 year subscription
when school Barmer has 2 year subscription
hospitalization and subscription fog which you
subscribe to. If we talk about Quid then Tide
appointed subscribe
please there is news whereas in ICICI Lombard's
Super Top Pay more than 150 and
organ donor both the companies now cover mistreatment for 2 minutes
which means any
such situation  In which the policy holder
cannot get admitted in the hospital,
in this hospital the policy holder can get the
treatment done from his home, which now the
school products cover this treatment i.e.
Ayurveda, Unani, Siddha and Homeopathy
treatment, both the companies now
cover this condition that the
hospital should be government, should be
government approved, if we
talk about ambulance then
300 hospitalizations in a Tata AIG,
when you subscribe for 500 in a school then you can do a maximum of 50
minutes on Tata Easy One, there
is an option in this that this should be for 2 years,
in which the registered
subscriber can, if we talk about no claim bonus then there is
Tides Pain No Claim Bonus,
whereas in this no claim bonus benefits
means that there is no earlier times like
this
Google option, range, speed, cat, mass sanitizer,
all this is not given to you by any insurance company
inbuilt, you have to do
job recruitment and not in such body
but in Tata Magic policy you
can select this optional on this condition that
if there is any disease then you can get
treatment outside India  You
can get your treatment done on requirement,
this facility is not available in this ward itself. If we
talk about doctors, then in TiG, there is 2 lakh
Sameer and Ghoshti
14 lakh and 5 lakh free existing
disease cover after 3 years in TiG and
2 years cover in this ward, re-tweet which is
a very good feature of ICC, on top of this,
whatever you do, after it gets over,
your subscription is reset once, it does
not give coverage to Aloe Vera, Tarzan
feet is not available, so
subscribe to both these companies, if
you liked the video, then actually
we keep bringing information, so
please like our channel and
subscribe,
Kwang you for watching